On the Spirit I must have
given at least, I don’t know,
about at least 100 lectures so far
only on the subject of Spirit.
So it’s an endless job.
And every time I say something people say,
“Mother you have said something very new.”
So the knowledge is endless
but you become the knowledge.
You yourself become the knowledge
and you start understanding it.
Only thing is, you must have, as a duty,
respect for yourself,
and the importance of responsibility
that you have to be the Spirit.
That’s why you have come
on this earth as human beings
at this time. This time is very precious
and it’s not a fashion to be a seeker.
But, it’s something that
has to happen to all of you.
Yesterday you people
asked me many questions
and I think I answered most of them.
Some of them were very good questions
but some were of them
a little very simple I think,
but nobody was aggressive.
But on the whole, I think that, maybe,
San Diego is a place from where
we may be able to save America.
I didn’t have any program anywhere
in Los Angeles or anything,
but I came to San Diego.
But you have to know that if this is the place
we have to get people who are of that quality,
I don’t know when are we going to get them.
But I hope we get those people of that quality.
Even a small nail can hold a sari.
In the same way, a little place
looking like San Diego
can save America.
May God bless you all.
So we'll have the experience now.
It will take about five minutes for you
because if all the chakras are discussed,
already the attention is on that.
It's very simple to put your hands towards me.
It's better. You've done a good job.
Just put your hands towards me.
Just like this.
Left.
Now, left hand towards me and
right hand towards the Mother Earth.
It will give you a balance. You need not
close your eyes just now, let's see.
Put your right hand towards the Mother Earth.
As I told you yesterday,
left side is our conditioning.
Conditioning, subconscious
and collective subconscious.
Very much at work here.
But also is an emotional side.
Now put your right hand towards me,
and left hand towards the sky.
Right hand towards me.
Right hand towards me like this.
Are you feeling the cool breeze in the hand?
You are already thoughtless. There's no thought.
But just see if you are feeling the cool breeze.
Are you?
Let's see.
All right?
Are you feeling any cool breeze in the hand?
All right, now put your
left hand on top of your head.
Just here. Fontanel bone area.
Are you feeling?
It's a very subtle thing.
Are you?
Pay attention.
Working out. Good?
All right. Now, change over.
See the left hand. With the right hand.
Just pay attention there, see.
Believe that you are the Spirit.
So just you have to say
in your heart, "I am the Spirit".
In your heart. Say it seven times.
It will work out.
Releasing.
Is it all right?
Are you feeling the heat coming out?
Little heat.
All right, now turn. Change. See now.
Right Swadhishthan.
All right?
Good? Amazing.
Now just see if it is working. Cool breeze.
Feel it. Just put your hands like this.
It's good.
You're all thoughtless. If you see,
there's no thought in your mind.
In complete silence.
Enjoy this.
This moment is going to transform your life,
take it from me.
You may not realise today,
but you’ll realise it very soon.
Ah. Strong.
Have faith in yourself, that’s the main thing.
It’s beautiful.
Now all those who are feeling the
cool breeze in the hand or in the head,
from the head, please raise your hands, all.
Both the hands like this.
Could you believe it?
Most of you.
May God bless you.
Except for one or two. Maybe you have come for
the first time. Have you come for the first time?
All right, maybe. We’ll see you, it’s not difficult.
Today it’s very powerful day. It's worked out.
Now know that you have found it,
but establish yourself.
This is very important is to establish.
Luckily you have a very good centre here.
And we have to work it out
through San Diego.
From this side and from New Jersey
from the other side.
You have to work it out.
All of you must remember
that you have got your realisation.
I don’t want to take any promises from you,
because I depend on your Spirit.
Respect it. Respect your realisation.
Respect yourself.
Now you will find you have a purpose in life,
and just understand how
this Divine power works.
And how we can manage it and control it.
How we can manoeuvre it, and how
it works in the larger interest,
in the higher interest, in the nobler
interest, in the righteous life.
You become that and others also become.
May God bless you.